machine learning teach a computer how to perform a task without explicitly
机器学习教计算机如何执行任务，而无需
programming it to perform said task instead feed data into an algorithm to
对其进行显式编程以执行所述任务，而是将数据输入算法以
gradually improve outcomes with experience similar to how organic life
逐步改善结果，其经验类似于有机生命的
learns the term was coined in 1959 by arthur samuel at ibm who was developing
学习方式，该术语是 1959 年由ibm 的亚瑟·塞缪尔（arthur samuel）创造的，他正在开发
artificial intelligence that could play checkers half a century later and
半个世纪后可以下棋的人工智能和
predictive models are embedded in many of the products we use every day which
预测模型嵌入在我们每天使用的许多产品中，这些产品
perform two fundamental jobs one is to classify data like is there another car
执行两项基本工作，一项是对数据进行分类，例如路上是否有另一辆车
on the road or does this patient have cancer the other is to make predictions
，或者该患者是否患有癌症 是
about future outcomes like will the stock go up or which youtube video do
对未来的结果进行预测，比如股票会涨还是你接下来想看哪个 youtube 视频
you want to watch next the first step in the process is to acquire and clean up
这个过程的第一步是获取和清理
data lots and lots of data the better the data represents the problem the
数据 大量的数据，数据越能代表问题
better the results garbage in garbage out the data needs to have some kind of
越好 结果垃圾中的垃圾数据需要有某种
signal to be valuable to the algorithm for making predictions and data
信号才能对算法进行预测 数据
scientists perform a job called feature engineering to transform raw data into
科学家执行一项称为特征工程的工作，将原始数据转换为
features that better represent the underlying problem the next step is to
更好地代表潜在问题的特征，下一步是
separate the data into a training set and testing set the training data is fed
将数据分成训练集和测试集，将训练数据
into an algorithm to build a model then the testing data is used to validate the
输入算法以构建模型，然后 测试数据用于验证
accuracy or error of the model the next step is to choose an algorithm which
模型的准确性或错误下一步是选择一种算法，该算法
might be a simple statistical model like linear or logistic regression or a
可能是一个简单的统计模型，如线性或逻辑回归，或者为
decision tree that assigns different weights to features in the data or you
数据中的特征分配不同权重的决策树，或者您
might get fancy with a convolutional neural network which is an algorithm
可能会得到 喜欢卷积神经网络，这是一种算法
that also assigns weights to features but also takes the input data and
，它也为特征分配权重，但也获取输入数据并
creates additional features automatically and that's extremely
自动创建附加特征，这
useful for data sets that contain things like images or natural language where
对于包含图像或自然语言等内容的数据集非常有用，在这些数据集中
manual feature engineering is virtually impossible every one of these algorithms
几乎不可能进行手动特征工程其中一种
learns to get better by comparing its predictions to an error function if it's
算法通过将其预测与 如果
a classification problem like is this animal a cat or a dog the error function
是分类问题，比如这个动物是猫还是狗，那么误差函数
might be accuracy if it's a regression problem like how much will a loaf of
可能是准确度 如果是回归问题，比如明年一条面包要花多少钱，
bread cost next year then it might be mean absolute error python is the
那么它可能意味着绝对误差 python 是
language of choice among data scientists but r and julia are also popular options
语言 数据科学家的选择，但 r 和 julia 也是流行的选择，
and there are many supporting frameworks out there to make the process
并且有许多支持框架可以使该过程变得
approachable the end result of the machine learning process is a model
平易近人机器学习过程的最终结果是一个模型
which is just a file that takes some input data in the same shape that it was
，它只是一个文件，它在同一个文件中获取一些输入数据 它被
trained on then spits out a prediction that tries to minimize the error that it
训练的形状然后吐出一个预测，试图最小化
was optimized for it can then be embedded on an actual device or deployed
它优化的错误然后可以嵌入到实际设备上或部署
to the cloud to build a real world product this has been machine learning
到云中以构建一个真实世界的产品，这已经是
in 100 seconds like and subscribe if you want to see more short videos like this
100 秒内的机器学习 如果您想看到更多这样的短视频，请点赞并订阅，
and leave a comment if you want to see more machine learning content on this
如果您想在此频道上看到更多机器学习内容，请发表评论，
channel thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
谢谢观看，我下一篇见